[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nelsons Column, built to commemorate Admiral Horatio Nelsons death, is a monument in this famous London square.", "correct_answer": "Trafalgar Square", "incorrect_answers": ["Soho Square", "Leicester Square", "Piccadilly Circus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first mention of any disappearances in the region was made in this year.", "correct_answer": "1950", "incorrect_answers": ["1894", "1974", "1912"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1078, a battle between two rulers was averted because of a chess game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where can you find a city named Orange?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "Texas", "Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which state produces the most maple syrup in New England?", "correct_answer": "Vermont", "incorrect_answers": ["Maine", "Massachusetts", "New Hampshire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these chemical compounds is added to table salt as an anti-caking agent?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Calcium carbonate", "Magnesium carbonate", "Tricalcium phosphate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A shade of what color is the color called jazzberry jam?", "correct_answer": "Red-violet", "incorrect_answers": ["Mint green", "Golden brown", "Fuchsia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Academy Awards did the 2005 movie King Kong win?", "correct_answer": "Best Visual Effects", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Best Actress", "Best Art Direction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Indian Ink comes from what country?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Japan", "United States", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whiteflies generally feed on what?", "correct_answer": "Leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruit", "Insects", "Carrion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Healthy people over 17 can donate what part of their blood every two weeks?", "correct_answer": "Platelets", "incorrect_answers": ["White blood cells", "Blood serum", "Red blood cells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor was interested in the role of The Joker in the 2008 movie The Dark Knight before it was given to Heath Ledger?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Carell", "Adrien Brody", "Robin Williams"]}]